fuckbook.xxx 2015-03-23

# Privacy Policy - Fuckbook

**

NOTICE: LAST UPDATED: March 13, 2015

** **

www.fuckbook.xxx IS INTENDED FOR CONSENTING ADULTS, OVER AGE 18, OR INDIVIDUALS THAT HAVE REACHED THE AGE OF MAJORITY IN THEIR APPLICABLE JURISDICTION, WHICHEVER IS OLDER.

**

Persons under the age of majority are not eligible to register for, use and/or purchase the services and/or products featured on www.fuckbook.xxx (“Website”) or to become a member. www.fuckbook.xxx does not knowingly collect information from children under 18 years of age. 

### Summary of Privacy Policy

This Policy applies to customer information we collect through our websites (for purposes of this Policy, “websites” includes mobile applications). Your privacy is important to us and we want you to clearly understand how information provided by you, or collected during your use of the website, is utilized to make your visit more enjoyable and to bring to you information and opportunities that may be of interest. 

### Information We Collect

We collect your information from the following sources: 

  * Information you give us, including through website registrations, creation of profiles and other information voluntarily supplied by you through posting on the website or engaging in media such as chat. 
  * Information automatically collected when you visit or use our websites, such as IP address, browser type and via cookies, analytic tools and third-party services in the same fashion as most other websites. 
  * Our mobile applications collect certain information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you use and the location of your device. You must first provide permission through your device before the application obtains such location information from technologies like GPS. (If applicable). 

### How We Use and/or Disclose Your Information

  * We use your information to enhance our provision of services to you. 
  * We may combine all the information we collect from users to determine ways in which our website and offerings can be improved. 
  * We may disclose or transfer your personal information from time to time to affiliates and third parties to help with our business operations and to bring to you offers that we believe might be of interest to you. 
  * We may contact you by email for customer service purposes as well as to make you aware of specials, new services and opportunities from our marketing customers. 
  * We also use such information to protect you, other users and the integrity of our website against fraud or as may be required by law. 
  * We want to communicate with you in ways you want to hear from us. Examples include email newsletters, special offers, and new product announcements. We will not contact you via phone or text message without your express consent (opt-in). We use an opt-out standard for all communications other than administrative communication concerning your account. 
  * We participate in re-marketing and interest-based advertising with Google and other companies. This means that you may see advertising on our website tailored to how you browse or shop, or you may see advertising on other websites based on your browsing behavior across websites. Learn how to opt-out from participating by [clicking here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

**

### FULL PRIVACY POLICY

**

### What This Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of information gathered when you are using or accessing the Services. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any information about you that our partners share with us or that we share with our partners. 

We are committed to protecting our user’s privacy. This Privacy Policy sets forth the policies and practices with respect to information or data gathered regarding registered users and members of the www.fuckbook.xxx website and/or other domains, products, advertising products, services, and/or content, including iOS, Android, and Windows Phone mobile application (collectively, the “Website”). While this Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any information about you that our partners share with us or that we share with our partners, you should understand that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of such third parties. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of all third-party websites you access. Additionally, this Privacy Policy does not govern what our registered users and members do on their individual www.fuckbook.xxx pages and we hereby disclaim any and all responsibility for the information collected by us as a result of postings by users and members on their individual pages. 

### Changes To The Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice on the Website explaining that we are changing our Privacy Policy. If the manner in which we use personal information changes, we will notify our registered users and members by posting the changes on this Website and, in our sole discretion, we may send out an e-mail notification to our registered users and members notifying them of the changes. 

NOTICE: USE OF THIS WEBSITE BY A REGISTERED USER OR MEMBER CONSTITUTES AN EXPRESS ASSENT TO THE USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE WEBSITE. AGAIN, CAREFULLY READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT BECAUSE YOUR REGISTRATION AND MEMBERSHIP TO AND USE OF THIS WEBSITE WILL EXPRESSLY SIGNIFY THAT YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THAT YOU CONSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT REGISTER, BECOME A MEMBER, OR USE THIS WEBSITE. 

### Information We Gather Automatically (Non- Personal Technical Data)

Each time an individual visits the Website, our servers collect certain non-personal technical information, including, but not necessarily limited to, the visitor’s IP Address, referral data and browser/platform type. This information is recorded by the standard operation of our Internet servers. We also count, track, and aggregate a visitor’s activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at the Website (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Website, etc.). The information collected in this regard either cannot identify who you are as an individual or is not used in that manner. 

### IP Address

An “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer or by your Internet service provider whenever you are surfing the Internet. We may use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, the Website, registered users, members, affiliates or other third parties. An IP address can also provide some information concerning your whereabouts. We do this by converting your IP Address into a rough geographical location. We may merge information about visitors and the number of visits into group data, which may then, at our discretion, be shared on an aggregated basis with our third-party advertisers/affiliates. In those circumstances, your individual personal information is not disclosed, nor under those circumstances will we disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data without your permission. 

### Like Most Websites, We Use Cookies/Browser Information/Web Beacons

We use cookies to store your preferences and to record session information for purposes such as ensuring that you are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements or to customize advertising and web page content for individual registered users and members. Cookies also enable our own system to recognize you when you visit the Website again and enable us to improve our service to you. Cookies are text files that may be sent to and saved by your web browser when you access a website; your web browser stores these cookies in a way associated with each website you visit, and you can generally see your cookies through your browser settings, depending on what browser you’re using. You must enable cookies from the Website in order to use many of the functions of the Website. Nevertheless, if you wish to reject or disable our cookies, you can configure your browser to do so. Instructions for disabling cookies can likely be found in your browser’s “Frequently Asked Questions” section. Please note, however, that the Website allows third parties who are presenting advertisements on some of our web pages to set and access their cookies on your computer in a process that we do not control. Cookies may also be used to compile aggregate information about areas of the Website visited most frequently. We reserve the right to automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with the Website, such as your browser type and version, what sort of device you are using, your operating system and version, your language preference, the website or service that referred you to the Website, the date and time of each request you make to the Website, your screen display information, and information from any cookies we have placed on your web browser (as described hereinabove). We also sometimes detect whether you are using certain web browser extensions and store that information in a manner associated with your membership. 

Similarly, a web beacon or pixel are types of code used by web developers which may also be embedded in a web page or email, and allows us or a third-party to see that you have looked at a particular web page. From time to time, we may run limited-time studies using web beacons, sometimes with third parties, to, for example, measure the effectiveness of our advertising or e-mail marketing/communications. 

### Information Related To Your Mobile Device

We also reserve the right to collect and store information related to your mobile device. In some cases, either we, or our mobile analytic provider, may receive, generate, or assign your mobile device a unique identifier. We may also request you to provide your mobile number to enable new products and improve our product. Our mobile applications collect certain information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you use and the location of your device. You must first provide permission through your device before the application obtains such location information from technologies like GPS. 

### Required And/or Optional Information For Becoming A Registered User And Member

When any adult registered user logs on to the Website as a member of this Website, the registered user and/or member may provide certain personal, as well as demographic, information which may include, but is not necessarily limited to, their name, address, age, gender, e-mail address, username and password, personal interests or affiliations and geographical location. This Website collects any and all such information and includes it in its customer database. 

The choice to provide us with your personal information is always yours. However, your decision to withhold particular information may result in limiting our ability to respond to your inquiries or provide you with the services you requested. If a new purpose is identified for the use of the information collected, the new purpose will be explained in an updated privacy policy prior to its new use. Unless such new purpose is required by law, your consent is required before information can be used for that purpose. Your continued use of the Website after the posting of the revised privacy policy shall be considered consent to the new use of the information. Demographic information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with third parties, but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals at any time. Note that, during the membership process, third-party billing service providers will collect personally identifiable information required to process payments for the Website’s services. We retain information (name and address) to correctly identify you in dealings with these third-party billing service providers. The Website does not control any and all additional information gathered by third-party billing service providers. As such, please review the applicable third-party billing service provider’s Website for its own policies governing the collection and usage of such information. 

If the Website features or conducts any special events, special promotions, third-party offers, contests or polls, a registered user or member of the Website may be asked to provide information in order to participate. If the registered user and member voluntarily provide that information, all such information may be collected by the Website and included in its customer database. When a registered user or member of this Website requests web pages from the Website’s server or clicks on banners or other third-party hypertext links, the Website will automatically collect some information or data about the registered user or member, including the IP address of the registered user or member. The information collected may also indicate any special preferences or requests of the registered user or member. All such information and data will be collected by the Website and included in our customer database. If a registered user or member sends any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the Website, or any to any of the Website’s employees, agents or representatives, the Website may collect any information regarding that communication and include that information in its customer database. 

### Profile Information That You Provide and User Content

We encourage registered users to fill out their profiles as completely as possible. Any communications from other registered users are done via our internal systems, which are used to match the message to you and generate an e-mail notification without disclosing any information aside from your chosen screen name. Accordingly, other registered users may not obtain your personal contact information such as your name, email, or telephone number unless you share it with them. However, any and all personally identifiable information that you: (i) enter into your profile; (ii) include in communications with other registered users or members; (iii) disclose in any media (e.g., text, chat streams, graphical, audio, visual, or audio-visual); or (iv) post or display on the Website is indeed accessible by other registered users and members of the Website. We are therefore not responsible for the disclosure of your personal information in this manner, nor are we liable for any other privacy-related claims or issues arising from your own voluntary disclosure, posting or transmission of personal information via the Website. You hereby acknowledge and agree that you shall be solely responsible and liable for any and all damages, liability and/or other consequences, foreseen or unforeseen, of all information which you submit, publish, display, disseminate, or otherwise communicate through the Website even if a claim for damages or liability should arise after termination or cancellation of our services. 

### How We Use Your Personal Information

The personally identifiable information obtained from our users is used in a variety of ways. 

  * It may be used to create, modify, and maintain the personal profiles of the users, to serve search utilities, to implement the functionality of the web site, to track usage, to target advertising, and to make the use of its Services enjoyable and rewarding for everyone involved in it. 
  * You may be contacted by email to confirm or terminate registration, to notify you of changes in our Terms and Conditions, to deal with any issues particular to you, or to promote events, services, and/or products that we or third-party vendors may wish to bring to your attention. We may use personally-identifiable information in correspondence with the user or with any other person. 
  * We may license or enter in to agreements with third-parties to transfer or sell outright, the use of personally-identifiable information. 
  * We may use and disclose any information to anyone, when, in our judgment, it is necessary or expedient to do so for the protection of individuals’, other users’ or the publics’ property. 
  * We may transfer any or all of the information to any successor in interest as a result of the sale of the web site, its Services, or of a substantial part of its assets. 
  * We may use personally identifiable information about our users for any reasonable commercial purpose to further your enjoyment, or to bring you opportunities we believe may be of interest to you. 
  * We participate in interest-based advertising. Interest based advertisements are ads that are served to you based on your browsing behavior. The goal is to show you ads more tailored to your interests. Advertisements may relate to our site or to others. In addition, we belong to ad networks that may use your browsing history across participating websites to show you interest-based advertisements on those websites. You may see ads on participating websites based on how you browse our website and those sites. 
  * You may get more information on opting-out of either interest-based advertising on our website, or interest-based advertising on other sites, by [clicking here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

You may access third-party services through the Website by clicking on links from our third-party advertisers or business partners. We may also share information that you provide to us with those third-party providers. Be advised, however, that this Privacy Policy only governs information we collect and you are responsible for reading and understanding those third-party providers’ privacy policies. 

### How We Use Your E-Mail Address

As part of the Services, you may occasionally receive emails and other communications from us. Administrative communications relating to your Account (e.g., for purposes of Account recovery or password reset) are considered part of the Services for your Account, which you will not be able to opt-out from receiving. We also may send you other kinds of emails, of which you can opt-out by using the “Opt-Out” link in the emails themselves or going to the account section (link it) of your profile. By submitting your email address at the Website, you also agree to receive email marketing from us and our third-party advertisers. You may also opt-out from receiving marketing emails from third-party advertisers by clicking on the unsubscribe link on the email, following the instructions in the privacy policy of the third-party or going to the account section of your profile. For visitors located in the United States, you agree that registering or providing personal information to us constitutes consent, notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, that we or our designee retain the right, and you hereby expressly authorize us and/or our designee, to contact you via telemarketing or text messaging. Moreover, by registering with, or requesting information from us or another third-party advertisers at, or through, the Website, such action shall constitute your written consent to be contacted via e-mail, instant messaging, text messaging, direct mail and/or telemarketing by such third-party advertisers. 

### To Better Serve You, We Aggregate Information To Bring You Information That May Be Of Interest To You

We may share or disclose non-private information, aggregate information, or other non-personally identifying information with third parties that we do business with. 

### Website And Member Communications

Members of the Website can directly communicate with other members through messaging services that are part of the services we provide at the Website (e.g., mail, chat, or via comments). We may use personally identifiable information within your profile to send notifications of these communications to you, but your personally identifiable information is not disclosed to other members by us. 

The Website also directly communicates with registered users and members through e-mail, instant messaging, and in some cases, downloaded executables thereby allowing our registered users and members to receive information when they are not on the Website. Our registered users and members can thereby remain current on internal communications and updates from other registered users, members or from us directly. The Website may also use personally identifiable information within your profile to send information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as special banners and promotions. If you do not want us to send you information on other third-party services or products, please [contact us](https://www.fuckbook.xxx/about/contact). 

### Analytic Applications

Personal Data is also collected to enable us to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior. 

For example, Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. 

### Application Data Collected

Information collected automatically from this Application (or third-party services employed in this Application) may include: the IP addresses of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URL addresses or domain (Uniform Resource Identifier) or domain name, the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the user, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the user's IT environment. 

### Explanation of the Use of Application Data and User ID

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. In that regard, Google Analytics makes use of a feature called user ID. This setup allows for a more accurate tracking of users by associating that user with the same ID over various sessions and devices. It is set up in a way that doesn’t allow Google to personally identify an individual or permanently identify a particular device. 

The user ID extension might make it possible to connect Data from Google Analytics with other Data about the user collected by this Application. The opt-out link below will only opt you out for the device you are on, but not from tracking performed independently by us. Contact us via the email address provided in this privacy policy to object to the aforementioned tracking. To opt-out through the Google tool [click here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

### Referral Service

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about the Website, we will ask you for your friend’s contact information. The Website will automatically send your friend an e-mail inviting them to visit the Website. The Website maintains this information for the sole purpose of sending this e-mail and tracking the success of the referral. 

### Third-Party Advertisers

We are able to offer our services to you, in part, based on your willingness to be targeted by our third-party advertisers. By allowing us to make the information you supply available to our third-party advertising affiliates/partners, you will receive information on products and services that may be of interest to you. As set forth hereinabove, this information may also be shared with our third-party advertisers on an aggregate basis. Please be advised however, that we do not control, and are not responsible for, the practices of our third-party advertisers. Please review the terms and privacy policy of any third-party advertiser that you may choose to contact. 

### Third-Party Offers

From time to time, we may sponsor or co-sponsor sweepstakes, offers, products, contests, or other services or events of interest to our registered users and members. In order to receive such offers, products or services, sweepstakes, or contests, your personal information will be shared with such third-party companies. We do this to ensure that they may provide their products and/or services to you without mandating that you first have to re-register. You may opt-out of receiving these communications by [contacting us](https://www.fuckbook.xxx/about/contact). 

### Service Providers

Like many businesses, we sometimes hire other companies to present offers, products, contests, or other services or events of interest to our members and registered users. Service Providers may assist us, by way of example, in sending emails, maintaining databases, or providing hosting services. When we employ a Service Provider to perform a function of this nature, we provide it with the information that it needs to perform its specific function, which may include personal data and other information that you provide to us via the Website. Please keep in mind, though, that we do not control, and are not responsible for, the practices of our Service Providers. 

### Legal Requirements

We reserve the right to access and disclose any information as we reasonably believe is necessary, in our sole discretion, to (i) satisfy any law, regulation, legal process, governmental request, or governmental order, (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, trust and safety, or technical issues (including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of improving security and preventing fraud, spam, and malware), (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect the rights, property, health or safety of us, our users, any third-parties or the public in general, including but not limited to situations involving possible violence, suicide, or self-harm. Moreover, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third-party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time. By accepting this Privacy Policy and using the Website and/or the services hereon, you waive and hold us, as well as our affiliates, content providers, and the operators of the Website harmless from any and all claims resulting from any and all of the foregoing action or as a result of any law enforcement authority’s investigations or inquiries. 

### The Security Of Your Information

Consistent with the policies set forth herein, the Website has adopted and implemented reasonable, appropriate and technologically feasible procedures for maintaining the security, accuracy and integrity of all personal information relating to registered users or members that is collected by the Website to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of data. 

Your registration and member information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. We may enable additional security features in the future, in our sole discretion. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and information by creating a unique, secure, and protected password and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account on the Website. We seek to protect your information (including your account information) to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

All registered users or members should consider any information provided to or collected by the Website as non-confidential, and consequently the Website assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any subscriber is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient. 

### What Happens To Your Information If The Business Is Sold

As our business grows, there is always the possibility that we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, your information may be part of the transferred assets and you hereby consent to such transfer of your information. 

### Opt-Out Policy

To stop receiving future communications from us or to opt out of having your personal information shared with third parties, please [send us](https://www.fuckbook.xxx/about/contact) your registration information and e-mail address. To cancel your registration and/or membership, please [contact us](https://www.fuckbook.xxx/about/contact) with your registration information and e-mail address. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our services, you may correct, update or cancel your registration and/or membership, and/or deactivate your account, by [contacting us](https://www.fuckbook.xxx/about/contact). 

### Questions About the Privacy Policy

If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please [contact us](https://www.fuckbook.xxx/about/contact).
